**Amir Kishk** 

Branilaca Šipa 19H, 71000 Sarajevo

Date of birth: 16<sup>th</sup> of February 1990. Nationality: Egyptian

Phone Number +38761830129. E-mail kishk.amir@gmail.com

**SUMMARY:** 

With six years of comprehensive professional experience, I have excelled in

drafting, reviewing, and negotiating a wide array of commercial contracts,

effectively representing my employer's interests in negotiations with external

parties. My expertise spans various types of agreements, including Messaging

Service Agreements, Supplier Agreements, Bilateral Agreements, Strategic

Partnership Agreements, Service Level Agreements, Non-disclosure Agreements,

and Data Processing Agreements. Additionally, I have demonstrated leadership

hiring and mentoring four members, two legal associates, one regional counsel,

and one legal intern. Moreover, my contributions extend to the successful

incorporation of three legal entities in the MENA region, alongside drafting and

implementing internal policies within the Legal department.

**EDUCATION:** 

2016 - 2018: International University of Sarajevo, Sarajevo, Bosnia & Herzegovina

MA. Student in International Relations.

4014 – 2015: Tanta University, Tanta, Egypt – Economic Sciences Diploma.

2008 - 2011: Cairo University, Cairo, Egypt – Bachelor of Law.

**EMPLOYMENT:** 

Apr 2022 – Present: INFOBIP – Counsel

Counsel works closely with work unit responsible person and/or Senior Counsels

and all relevant internal and external stakeholders on complex global and/or

regional projects and initiatives that fall under the assigned area of work. Gives

accurate and timely counsel and assistance to management, internal and external

stakeholders, in a variety of legal topics covered under the assigned area.

Nov 2020 – Apr 2022: INFOBIP – Senior Legal Associate

Senior Legal Associate is working as a proficient and well-integrated part of the

team. In addition to carrying out regular tasks associated with responsibilities of

specific work unit, Senior Legal Associate tasks will include handling more

complex tasks under some supervision, research, reviewing and monitoring

current processes, drafts, policies, and applicable regulation and providing

recommendations to enhance company processes, policies and procedures. Has a

strong knowledge and recognized set of skills applied in managing tasks.

Apr 2018 - Nov 2020: INFOBIP - Legal Associate

The Legal Associate is an entry-level position in each given work unit. The Legal

Associate is primarily working with the team carrying out regular tasks associated

with a specific work unit, and under close supervision of seniors delivers outputs

in a timely and organized manner.

February 2017 – June 2017: (part-time) Social Studies Teacher at Al-Amal School

Oct 2011 - Dec 2015: Fayez Kishk Law Firm

## Language Skills:

- Arabic: Mother tongue.
- English: Fluent speaking and writing (General Conversation)
- Bosnian: beginner speaking and writing (General Conversation)